https://sufism.org/privacy-policy

Skip to content
Privacy Policy
Home/Privacy Policy
Privacy Policyadmin2017-01-29T15:59:40-05:00
Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the https://sufism.org and The Threshold Society and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to The Threshold Society include https://sufism.org and Threshold. The Threshold website is a Spiritual and Educational site. By using the Threshold website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Threshold may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase Threshold’s products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Threshold. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Threshold website.
Threshold encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Threshold so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Threshold is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Threshold website.
Use of your Personal Information
Threshold collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.
Threshold may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Threshold and its affiliates. Threshold may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Threshold does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
Threshold may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Threshold, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Threshold will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Threshold or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Threshold; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Threshold, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Threshold website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Threshold pages, or register with Threshold site or services, a cookie helps Threshold to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Threshold website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Threshold features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Threshold services or websites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol provided by Go Daddy Class 2 Certification Authority.
Children Under Thirteen
Threshold does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.
Disconnecting your Threshold Account from Third Party Websites
You will be able to connect your Threshold account to third party accounts. BY CONNECTING YOUR THRESHOLD ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES). IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED IN THIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THE THIS FEATURE. You may disconnect your account from a third party account at any time. Users may learn how to disconnect their accounts from third-party websites by visiting their “My Account” page. Users may also contact us via email or telephone..
Opt-Out & Unsubscribe
We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Threshold by following Manage Your Subscription link towards the bottom of the recent email you received from Threshold.
Changes to this Statement
Threshold will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Threshold encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Threshold is protecting your information.
Contact Information
Threshold welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Threshold has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Threshold at:
The Threshold Society
270 Quarter Horse Ln
Watsonville, California 95076
Email Address: mevlana@cruzio.com
Telephone number: (831) 685-3995
Effective as of February 29, 2012
Go to Top
